Let's look at the basic types of
communications.
So we have formal written.
All our project plans.
The project charter, of course,
very important document.
Contracts, agreements, complex technical
problems.
We don't want any misunderstanding,
so it'll be formal written.
And meeting minutes.
I hope everybody takes meeting minutes.
That's where it's decision.
are made and by documenting and publishing
those that's your CYA cover your assets I
had to find a nice way to say that
document decisions are made that's really
important okay informal written sending
out an email handwritten notes formal
verbal presentations the
speeches keynote whereas informal
verbal meetings and
conversations by the water cooler.
You know, those are informal verbal.
Pretty easy to understand.